The Guide to the Hiteman Leather Company records, 1898-1968
Hiteman Leather Company records, 1898-1968
- "Mrs. Dorothy Fox Davies": Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- "Department of Labor N.Y.S.": Correspondence, forms, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- "Department of Labor (Nature of Experience Rating Charges) Charts 1959": Charts, forms (Box 6, Folder 7)
- "Thomas Dorrity": Correspondence, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- "D": Orders, contract, correspondence, market reports, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- "Employees Mutual Liability (Insurance Co. of Wisconsin)": Correspondence, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- "Employers Mutual Liability Reports - 1959": Notices, workmens compensation forms, correspondence (Box 6, Folder 11)
- "H. Elkan Co.": Correspondence, hide market reports, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- "E": Correspondence, enclosures, hide market reports, orders, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- "Feakes Mercantile Agency": Credit reports, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- "F": Correspondence, enclosures, orders, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- "Ganey, Hagan and Company 1959": Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 16)
- "General Information": Movement reports in raw material, sales and inventory reports, notice to employees, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- "G": Orders, correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- "Thomas Hartnett - Orders": Orders, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- "Thomas Hartnett": Correspondence, notes, shipping notices, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- "Vogel Helmholz - 1959": Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 21)
- "Hospital Plan, Inc. 1959": Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 22)
- "Hide Sheets - 1959": Weekly reports on 'skins (Box 6, Folder 23)
- "In process - Inventory": In process inventory work sheets, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- "H": Invoices, reports of boiler inspection, correspondence, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- "I": Correspondence, weekly inventory reports, orders, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- "J": Correspondence, orders, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- "Kaufman Trading Corp. 1959": Calfskin auction results, credit memos, correspondence (Box 6, Folder 28)
- "K": Correspondence, invoices, leather sample, minutes - bc. of Directors meetings and letter from lawyer, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- "L": Correspondence, invoices, enclosures, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- "Marine Midland Bank and Trust Co.": Correspondence, interest memos, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- "Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. Reports 1959": Claim forms, form letters, correspondence (Box 6, Folder 32)
- "Milligan & Higgins: Duplicate bills and lading and postcards re goods received, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- "Mutual Shoe Company 1959": Orders, correspondence (Box 6, Folder 34)
- "M": Correspondence, orders, enclosures, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- "Mc": Correspondence, orders, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- "N": Correspondence, orders, fire insurance report, enclosures, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- "O": Correspondence, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- A.J. & J.O. Pilar, Inc. 1959": Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 39)
- "Post Office Box Rent, Insurance Registered 1959": Receipts (Box 6, Folder 40)
- "P": Correspondence, orders, leather samples, price lists for coloring, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- "Q": Correspondence, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- "R": Correspondence, orders, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- "S": Correspondence, invoices, shipping receipts, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- "Tanners' Council of America, Inc. Tanners Council News": Weekly newsletters, use of fish oil in tanning, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- "Tanners' Council of America, Inc. 1959": Industry news, leather samples, correspondence (Box 6, Folder 46)
- "Tanners' Council of America, Inc. Past Due Accounts": Reports, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- "Tanners' Council of America, Inc. Trade Survey Bureau 1959": Weekly reports of wettings and bookings (Box 6, Folder 48)
- "Town and Country Shoes 1959": Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 49)
- "Time Studies": Studies and notes, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- "T": Correspondence, orders, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- "U": Orders, invoices, correspondence, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- "Al Verdekal": Correspondence, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- "V": Correspondence, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- "U": Orders, correspondence, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- "Al Verdekal": Correspondence, reports, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- "A.L. Webster & Company": Weekly trade reports, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- "W": Correspondence, orders, enclosures, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- "V": Correspondence, orders, Utica Observer Dispatch. 10-27-60, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- "X-Y-Z": Orders, correspondence, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- "J.C. Andresen": Correspondence, reports, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- "A": Correspondence, enclosures, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- "Boot & Shoe Recorder": Correspondence, enclosures, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- "F. Brown Shoe Company": Correspondence, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- "B": Correspondence, enclosures, industry and economic newsletters and outlooks, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- "Calf Tanners Association": Reports, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- "Department of Commerce Bureau of Census": Reports, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- "C": Correspondence, enclosures, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- "Densten Felt and Hair Company": Correspondence, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- "D": Correspondence and enclosures, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- "Endicott Johnson Corp.": Correspondence, remittance advice, orders, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- "E": Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- "Feakes Mercantile Agency": Reports, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- "First Citizens Bank and Trust Co. Trends": Newsletter, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- "First Citizens Bank and Trust Company": Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- "Florsheim Shoe Company": Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- "F": Correspondence, enclosures, contract, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- "Ganey, Hornung & Hall": Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- "Daniel Green Co.": Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- "G": Correspondence and enclosures, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- "William B. Heald & Co. March 1941": Reports, correspondence, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- "William B. Heald & Co. February 1941: Reports, correspondence (Box 7, Folder 28)
- "William B. Heald & Co. January 1941": Correspondence and reports (Box 7, Folder 29)
- "William B. Heald & Co. December 1940": Correspondence and reports (Box 7, Folder 30)
- "William B. Heald & Co. November 1940": Correspondence and reports (Box 7, Folder 31)
- "William B. Heald & Co. October 1940": Reports and correspondence (Box 7, Folder 32)
- "William B. Heald and Co., September 1940": Reports and correspondence (Box 7, Folder 33)
- "William B. Heald & Co. Orders": Orders, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Wm. B. Heald & Co. Account of Sales": Sales receipts and summaries, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- "Hiteman Leather Company, Inc.": Memos, notes, legal documents, personnel information, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- "Hudson Mohawk Mutual Casualty Co. Reports": Reports of injuries, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- "Hudson Mohawk Mutual Casualty Co.": Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- "Hungerford & Tersy": Correspondence, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- "H": Correspondence and enclosures, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- "I": Correspondence and enclosures, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- "Johnstown Wool Shoe Company": Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- "J": Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- "K": Correspondence, newsletters, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- "Herman Loewenstein Jan. 1, 1941 to April 1, 1941" (Box 7, Folder 45)
- "Hermann Loewenstein Sept. 1, 1940 to Jan. 1, 1941: Correspondence and reports, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- "Hermann Loewenstein Account of Sales January 1, 1941 to April 1, 1941: Invoice duplicates, sales summary, adding machine types (Box 7, Folder 47)
- "Hermann Loewenstein Account of Sales Sept. 4, 1940 thru Dec. 26, 1940: Invoices, summaries, adding machine types (Box 7, Folder 48)
- "Hermann Loewenstein Orders": Orders, leather samples, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- "Department of Labor": Reports, correspondence, bulletins, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- "L": Correspondence, orders, enclosures, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- "Hugh Carville, Correspondence": Correspondence, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- "Carlisle Shoe Company": Orders, correspondence, leather samples, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- "Carmo Shoe Manufacturing Co.": Correspondence, orders, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- "C": Correspondence, orders, enclosures, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- "William P. Davidson": Correspondence, reports, orders, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- "Wm. P. Davidson, orders", 1960 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- "Thomas Dorrity": Correspondence, reports, leather swatches, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- "Howard Dietrich & Son": Market reports, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- "Mrs. Dorothy Fox Davies": Correspondence, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- "Dept. of Labor, N.Y. State": Newsletters, correspondence, statistics, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- "Dept. of Labor (Nature of Experience Rating Charge) Charts": Correspondence, charts, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- "D": Correspondence, orders, enclosures, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- "H. Elkan & Co.": Market reports, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- "Employer's Mutual Liability (Insurance Company of Wisconsin)": Reports, correspondence, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- "Employer's Mutual Liability Reports": Disability reports, physicians reports, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- "E": Orders, reports, correspondence, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- "Feakes Mercantile Agency": Credit reports, correspondence, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- "F": Correspondence, orders, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- "General Information": Inventory report other movement reports, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- "G": Orders, correspondence, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- "Thomas Hartnett Orders": Orders, correspondence, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- "Thomas Hartnett": Correspondence, orders, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- "Vogel Helmholz": Correspondence, reports, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- "Hospital Plan, Inc.": Correspondence, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- "H": Correspondence, orders, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- "I": Correspondence, orders, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- "In Process Inventory": Inventory report, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- "J": Correspondence, orders, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- "Kaufman Trading Corp.": Auction results, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- "K": Correspondence, orders, contract, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- "L": Correspondence, orders, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- "Marine Midland Bank & Trust Co.": Correspondence, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- "Metropolitan Life Insurance Co.": Correspondence, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- "Milligan & Higgins": Freight bills, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- "Mutual Shoe": Correspondence and orders, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- "M": Correspondence, orders, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- "Mc": Correspondence, orders, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- "N": Correspondence, market report and newsletters, orders, leather sample, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- "O": Correspondence, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- "P. O. Box Rent, Ins., Registered: Receipts, record of meter register readings, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- "P": Correspondence, orders, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- "Q": Correspondence, orders, leather samples, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- "R": Correspondence, orders, reports, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- "S": Correspondence, orders, enclosures, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- "Tanners' Council of America, Inc. Trade Survey Bureau, 1960": Weekly reports (Box 8, Folder 45)
- "Tanners' Council of America": Newsletters, industry reports, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- "Tanners' Council of America - (Past Due Accounts)": Reports, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- "Town & Country Shoes": Correspondence, orders, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- "Time Studies": Study and memo, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- "Tanners Council of America, Inc. (Tanners Council News)": Trade newsletter, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- "T": Correspondence, orders, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- "Employers Mutual Liability (Ins. Co. of Wisconsin)": Correspondence, reports, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- "H. Elkan Co.": Trade reports, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- "Employers Mutual Liability Report (per Mr. Mandig): Claim forms, correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- "E": Correspondence, invoices, enclosures, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- "Feakes Mercantile Agency": Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- "Film Star Creations": Correspondence, enclosures, forms, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- "F": Correspondence, invoices, enclosures, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- "Ganey, Hagan & Company": Correspondence, reports, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- "G": Invoices, correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- "General Information": Inventory reports, sales and purchase reports, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- "Thomas Hartnett": Correspondence, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- "Thomas Hartnett (Orders)": Invoices, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- "Hide Sheets": Weekly accounting of hides", 1961 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- "Hospital Plan, Inc.": Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- "H": Contract, correspondence, enclosures, orders, industry reports and newsletters, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- "I": Correspondence, enclosures, orders, sales brochures, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- "J": Invoices, correspondence, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- "Kaufman Trading, Inc.": Reports on calfskin auctions, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- "K": Correspondence, invoices, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- "L": Correspondence, invoices, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- "Metropolitan Life Insurance Co.": Age classification summary, correspondence, death claim, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- "Marine Midland Bank & Trust Company": Correspondence, newsletters, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- "Milligan & Higgins": Bills of lading, load information, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- "M": Correspondence, bills, enclosures, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- "Mc": Correspondence and enclosures, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- "N": Correspondence, enclosures, industry newsletters, invoices, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- "O": Correspondence and enclosures, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- "(Copies of Promotional Letters Holiday, Etc.)": Advertisement, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 28)
- "P. O. Box Rent - Ins. Registered": Receipts, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- "P": Correspondence, enclosures, bills, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- "Q": Purchase orders, correspondence, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- "R": Correspondence, enclosures, orders, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- "Swatch Book Orders for spring - 1962, Fall 1961": Correspondence and orders (Box 9, Folder 33)
- "Requests for fall, 1962": Correspondence and orders, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- "S": Correspondence, orders, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- "Tanners Council of America (past due accounts)": Report, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- "Tanners Council of America": Survey reports, correspondence, industry news and information, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- "Tanners Council of America (Trade Summary Bureau 1961)": Weekly reports on meetings, bookings, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- "Town & Country Shoes": Correspondence, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- "Time Studies": Work sheet, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 40)
- "Tanners Council of America (Tanners Council News)": Industry newsletter, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- "Miss Marianne Tater": Correspondence on colors, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- "Al Verdekal": Correspondence, orders, 1 sample of leather, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- "T": Correspondence, blueprint of wash & drain mill Adapter, orders, price list, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- "U file - replacing lost 'U' ": Correspondence, orders, leather samples, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- "V": Industry news, correspondence, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- "A.L. Webster & Co.": Correspondence, industry news, market conditions and prices, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- "W": Correspondence and enclosures, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- "X-Y-Z": Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- "Wires": Telegrams, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- "Letters to All Agents": Correspondence, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- "Alpine Leather Co., Orders": Orders, correspondence, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- "American Appraisal Company": Correspondence, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- "Aulson Tanning Machinery Co.": Correspondence, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- "Alpine Leather Company": Correspondence, leather sample, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- "A": Correspondence, enclosures, purchase orders, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- "Bootmaker": Correspondence, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- "Parker Bowman": Correspondence and reports, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- "Mr. Sidney Brown": Correspondence and reports, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- "B": Correspondence, orders, sawdust sample, enclosures, leather sample, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- "S": Correspondence and enclosures, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- "Tanners Council of America February 1945": Newsletter, correspondence (Box 10, Folder 2)
- "Tanners Council of America January 1945": Newsletter, correspondence (Box 10, Folder 3)
- "Tanners Council America - December 1944": Newsletters, proceedings of annual meeting (Box 10, Folder 4)
- "Tanners Council of America - November 1944": Newsletters, correspondence, reports (Box 10, Folder 5)
- "Tanners Council of America - October 1944": Reports, newsletter, correspondence (Box 10, Folder 6)
- "Tanners Council of America - September 1944": Reports, newsletters (Box 10, Folder 7)
- "Tanners Council of America - August 1944": Newsletter, reports (Box 10, Folder 8)
- "Tanners Council of America - July 1944": Reports, newsletter, correspondence (Box 10, Folder 9)
- "Tanners Council of America - June 1944": Newsletter, reports (Box 10, Folder 10)
- "Tanners Council of America - May 1944": Reports, newsletters (Box 10, Folder 11)
- "T": Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- "United Eastern Coal Sales Corp.": Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- "U": Correspondence and enclosures, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- "V": Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- "War Production Bd. Government Orders and Releases - Mch. 1944-Mch. 1945": Directives and reports, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- "War Production Board May 1944 to Nov. 1944": Correspondence, reports, enclosures (Box 10, Folder 17)
- "War Price and Rationing Board": Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- "War Manpower Commission": Correspondence, enclosures, 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- "War Production Board Industrial Salvage Branch": Salvage report forms and correspondence, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- "War Production Board Quebracks inventory and consumption reports": Report, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- "A.L. Webster & Co. February 1945": Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 22)
- "A.L. Webster & Co. January 1945": Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 23)
- "A.L. Webster & Co. December 1944": Correspondence, orders (Box 10, Folder 24)
- "A.L. Webster & Co. November 1944": Correspondence, reports (Box 10, Folder 25)
- "A.L. Webster & Co. October 1944": Correspondence, reports (Box 10, Folder 26)
- "A.L. Webster & Co. September 1944": Correspondence, reports (Box 10, Folder 27)
- "A.L. Webster & Co. August 1944": Correspondence, reports (Box 10, Folder 28)
- "A.L. Webster & Co. July 1944": Reports, correspondence (Box 10, Folder 29)
- "A.L. Webster & Company June 1944": Reports and correspondence (Box 10, Folder 30)
- "A.L. Webster & Company May 1944": Reports, correspondence (Box 10, Folder 31)
- "W": Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- "X-Y-Z": Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- "Absentee Report": Reports, 1959-1961 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- "Remittance": Invoices and remittance statements, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- "Wires": Telegrams and copies, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- "Letters to All Agents": Correspondence, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- "American Appraisal Co.": Correspondence, bulletin, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- "Aulson Tanning Machinery Co.": Correspondence, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- "Alpine Leather Co.": Correspondence, sample shoe part, invoices, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- "Alpine Leather Co. (Orders)": Orders, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- "A": Invoices, correspondence, enclosures, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- "Parker Bowman. Orders": Orders, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- "Parker Bowman": Correspondence, shipping records, invoices, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- "Mr. Sidney Brown": Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- "B": Correspondence, invoice, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- "Carlisle Shoe Co. Orders": Invoices, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- "Carlisle Shoe Company": Correspondence and invoices, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- "Carmo Shoe Manufacturing Co.": Correspondence, invoices, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- "C": Correspondence, invoices, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- "William P. Davidson": Correspondence, invoices, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- "William P. Davidson (Orders)": Invoices, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- "Dept. of Labor, New York State": Correspondence, forms, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- "DiPariyi": Correspondence and enclosures, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- "Thomas Dorrity": Correspondence, reports, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- "Dept. of Labor - Federal": Directive, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 56)
- "D": Correspondence, invoices, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- "Tanners' Council of America (past due accounts)": Reports, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- "Miss Marianne Tater": Correspondence, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- "Town and Country Shoes": Orders and invoices, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- "Time Studies": Hand written rating sheets, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- "T": Orders, correspondence, enclosures, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- "U": Correspondence, orders, invoices, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- "Al Verdekal": Correspondence, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- "V": Correspondence, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- "A. L. Webster & Co.": Hide and skin sales reports, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- "W": Correspondence, orders, enclosures, invoices, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- "A": Invoices, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- "B": Invoices, 1915-1916 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- "C": Invoices, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- "D": Invoices, 1915-1916 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- "E-F": Invoices, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- "G": Invoices, 1915-1916 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- "H-I-J": Invoices, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- "K-L": Invoices, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- "M": Invoices, 1915-1916 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- "N-O": Invoices, 1915-1916 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- "P-Q": Invoices, 1915-1916 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- "R": Invoices, 1915'1916 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- "S": Invoices, 1915-1916 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- "T-U-V": Invoices, 1915-1916 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- "W": Invoices, 1915-1916 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- "A": Correspondence - Boston store, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- "B": Correspondence, invoices, leather samples, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- "C": Correspondence, bills, orders, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- "D": Correspondence, orders, reports, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- "E": Correspondence, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- "F": Correspondence, orders, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- "G": Correspondence, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- "H": Correspondence, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- "I-J-K": Correspondence, bills, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- "L-M": Orders, correspondence, reports, leather sample, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- "N-P": Correspondence, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- "R": Shipping memo, invoice, leather sample, correspondence, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- "S": Correspondence, cancelled checks, orders, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- "T": Correspondence, reports, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- "U-V": Reports, correspondence, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- "W": Fall market reports, orders, correspondence, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- "Sidney Brown": Invoices, correspondence, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- "B": Correspondence, bills, enclosures, newsletters, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 2)